Do they know we're 4, 1, 1, 2, 5?
We have the invitation, but we're able to all of them,
to just convert them to various ways of wealth.
Let us pray.
Almighty God, you give us new life, new hope,
and new opportunities with each day.
Help us to use these blessings to the best of our abilities
in doing the work before us,
devoting ourselves to your service,
and putting our selfish interests aside
to seek the welfare of our community.
Direct us a Lord in all our doings
with your most gracious favor,
and further us with your continual help,
that in all our work begun, continued, and ended in you.
We make glorify your name in Jesus' name, we pray, amen.
Congratulations to the flag of the United States of America.
And to either it by look for ways of faith,
one nation under God, individual,
will never be in justice for all.
I'd like to get that.
Well, again, but I'm just a personal person.
Five.
Five, eight, nine, plus.
Second.
Five, B, Tehra Tehra, Tehra,
Tehra, Tehra, Tehra, Tehra, Tehra,
Tehra, Tehra, Tehra, Tehra, Tehra, Tehra,
and associate with complaint fraidings in the amount of $5,000.
Guess where this is for...
um...
I'm doing some modeling and everything for the relicensing.
If this is approved at night,
we will have a remating balance of $709,650 in 20 cents per year.
What's true, approved?
Second.
All right.
Yo, whose name?
Barman,kook,
Burger?
Remember on this, can I ask you to question the...
the civil case, five C, minutes from the 20th, October 21st, 2025,
ringing me.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Don't go.
Hi.
Be set.
Jones.
Aye.
Furns.
Second.
Don't go.
Aye.
Furns.
Jones.
Aye.
Furns.
Motion to approve.
Second.
All right.
Joe's time.
5F.
The Greenland Colby Island and on the talent science studios, which includes the transfer
of landing him for a credit for the new sign of the turn-by conference and the new
sign in front of the new dollar general on the board of the land checking out.
Kevin.
I brought this before you last week.
I thought it was a win-win, though.
This is the agreement between the MSUA and Alan size.
It allows us to give it up some blocks that are just in Vegas.
And it's changed for two new beds.
The time clock and winning for a dollar general after talking to the authority that was
here last week.
They wanted to go back to the drawing more to a bit just to get some other ideas.
So I went back to Colby and kind of told him what we talked about.
And he came up with some other options.
So this was the original sign that he came up with.
He came up with a dollar general.
He didn't really like this one.
He asked him to bring back some other ideas.
But this will be neon.
It's going to leave up.
So on this, on this sign, it was neon.
It came around it.
The moment of the whole was neon.
Each one of them was done.
This one came from dollar general.
This is for the dollar general.
So this is the one that I wanted to let this mother on.
This is the sign that's going to go up.
I'd like everybody to bring it all in the eye.
I'd like that.
Yep.
So here's some other options that I came up with.
And this is to replace the product dollar general.
Hold the color.
Get my sign.
It's hard to type the same sign.
Just different font.
Go back.
There's square sixes.
Good.
Screw sixes.
Still.
Get all neon.
Everything's neon.
I don't know.
I don't know anything about it.
We got it in here.
We're three.
It's kind of your retro.
It's like you.
You'll clear that down.
That's all.
That's me in the 50s.
How tall is that guy?
I'm just kidding.
Sign number four.
I hear their voices.
They.
That dude's probably six feet, so it's probably-
It's probably-
It's our current case on that.
And then again, this five and six is the same size, just with the different lettering.
And it kind of looks like someone with an intern.
The back-down mounts the front there.
Is that going to have the star on one side and that on the other side?
This is just-
Oh, that's just a reference of what I've been there today.
I've got you.
Oh, it's just a reference.
Not, wow, that's-
No, no.
There's your last one.
I've got you.
And then there's your last one.
On that one, Kevin, is that lit up on the 66?
It is.
The round here is lit up.
No, the home is lit up.
So he hasn't really had time to break it down.
Because he just wins a-
Or, lastly, I doubt whether we got it back to his front.
So there may be a price difference.
He says, we'll be out of that umbrella.
About 3500 plus or minus.
Which costs $50.
But he just doesn't go through one line track.
If you have lots of things.
You know what I mean?
But he's going to go up on it.
You want to see something else, throw back to go again.
I like this one.
And the font matches-
Let's get into that.
Going on the front.
The font.
The font matches.
You want to kind of deal together a little bit.
Last one.
On the seventh.
On the stars.
On the hearts of the bottom.
Then they lit up.
The lights.
On the two.
What's your thoughts, Brian?
I like this one too.
Can we put Mayor's face on there?
No, because then we'd have bullet holes in it.
Our taser mark.
No, I like this one a lot.
I think that right there, I like the way that the bombs match and they kind of look like they
go together.
We're kind of closing this back side.
That's going to be facing the street.
So we're just, you know, for the last ringer, just a panel.
Yeah.
So we're kind of used with that round.
And that kind of gives it that retro look too.
Oh, shout out how it's the 266 on it.
Kevin, do you?
Well, they put ballers around it.
Or is there already ballers around?
So nobody backs into it.
I knew that was coming so that the side to the left side will face the street
So it's going to set perpendicular to the street right so that edge is going to face the street
We should put our established here there
On that on this end. I established whatever
Thank you. I just learned that the other day. I shouldn't have been in my leadership lane in the class
Other than that, I'll thank you. That's probably the one. I like that because it gives that
Retro load of the matches the sign by the turn bike
Still got the me on and lit up
Cool
That was too easy
Kind of gives it the pin blue line but to actually I mean that's kind of what I thought at first
So I guess before we don't have anything
Like it
Make a motion we approve two signs
We agree to vote on the agreement make a motion of privy group
He wanted to get this approved because he wants to get these dead as soon as possible before
Appreciate it
Good job
5G
Memorandum of understanding with the
Ottawa County Parks and Humanities Council for the use of main attractions building
Look at one 13 north main from year of last 20
So I'm here on behalf of I'm the Secretary of Bill and so this year
We're keeping with
Centennial
So they will be
Specific arts if you look in your packet
For example, it's of the artwork the main attraction building
I'm gonna I'll be back at city council to talk to you up the next one
is the artist that you see in your packet looks like there's flowers in wildlife, but they'll be specific to my amendment of the whole theme for that art, we'll be submitted before it's painted, and we brought for the committee that just because stout is heading on part of that committee too, so that this year we're trying to keep it not so much abstract art and some other kind of things that we've done in the past is sure we all,
in terms of this continual travelers and this time. So what we're trying to do this in my view, and I appreciate this view, we've got it just right before you can get over to, so this is our agreement that we need for the guys to be able to paint on for this, it was you, and so it will be on the art park.
So our goal is to prep that entire wallpaper up there to be able to stay for a year.
We paint from the piano that we paint for the artist, we get, we don't ever go with the best time to use the symbol, usually go for it, which is, they schedule out way for it.
So the picture is that what's going to be painted there?
No, that's an example of that.
What their style is, the other one that you sound like the buffalo, that's the one that buffalo is going to be on that.
That's really cool.
It is. My understanding, we talked about it.
I'm nervous. You know, that lip word, Jessica painted the photo op on that one.
And we're going to use some interns and think like that.
So we're teaching students, 14 adults to, in our classes and think like that, use the internet.
They want, they don't all be painted, but your best is this week.
I have some students currently that have participated in their internships, and they've benefited greatly from it.
Yeah, they're selling good.
There's going to be more opportunity for one that will be some interns projects that we're doing to,
for doing too.
And I did talk to the guy on the mirror, where one of these, oh, yes, he said, I'm the sheriff talked about putting something on side of jail to anybody, I know that's not ours, but
I know that we can't because a lot of times one of these artists are in town because we think for him tells him things like that. So sometimes those artists will take on it.
If you make these artists, I suggest they get all the Callie of the Library really clever me and we can set them up on those artists that are interested.
You might talk to them.
That's amazing artists that we've had to stick to securely art early on.
You might talk to him because he had mentioned it one day.
It's been a while, but he had mentioned it.
Maybe all of these artists are here, they're always looking to push him up.
They tell me it takes like two to four days.
Some of them come in early if it's really big and get started.
And if you don't have much money, we get on the, it'll be a pretty good size,
because we've got quite a bit of a mark for this one on the main interaction building.
I don't think we have enough to do the entire while, but we're going to present it.
All right.
Thanks for joining us.
Other new business, if any of which is the reason for posting this in the seven trustee community now,
8 trust my communications.
Yes, sir.
9 adjournment.
Motion.
Second.
He said.
All right.
Gentlemen, I've barred to five.
Five.